Vatsal ji, now this is my question to you that
which stock is on your radar or which
are the set of stocks that you are
recommending to your clients,
sir there are two stocks on my radar, first is
PVR which belongs to the media industry, it belongs to the
entertainment industry,
basically sir there are two reasons for this, one is fundamental reason and
second is technical reason,
fundamentally sir, PVR has made a
lot of changes in its business model, its
business model was earlier capital intensive.
Trying to lighten it up a bit.
And recently PVR has
also turned from a loss making company to a profitable one.
And the way I see it, the
trend of movies has changed in the last two years,
as earlier it was the case that if any
major superstar was coming, then his film itself was
giving a big box office collection.
But currently, even the small productions are
giving box office collection of ₹100 crores.
And the way PVR has
sustained at the level of 1100, from here
we have very little to lose in the stock
but from here we can easily see 30 to 40%
gains in it.   So this will be
my first stock.  My second stock
will be ICICI LBD.  ICICI has also
recently made a good change
in its business model and I would like to say one thing that it is a very good
general insurance player in the
private sector
and the way it has shown consolidation at the levels of 2000
and also the
government is highly promoting
insurance so I can see that
from here we can see a good breakout
in ICICI LBAD and with this I
think in the next one to two months this
stock can easily show a move of ₹100 to ₹200 from here.
Ok.  So you can watch these two counters
because these are on Vatsal ji's radar
and Vatsal ji is bullish on them.  Okay
Vatsal ji, thank you very much
for joining us today and giving us your valuable time.
Thank you so much.
Thank you sir.   Thank
you.